<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<resources>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open sliding pane</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close sliding pane</string>
    <string name="menu_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="menu_next">Next</string>
    <string name="menu_prev">Prev</string>
    <string name="tutorial_welcome">AnExplorer is a file explorer with a Zing!!!\n
        You can do lot more than just exploring your files.\n\n
        This tutorial gets you through the major stuff you can do with AnExplorer</string>
    <string name="tutorial_overview"> You can see the overview of all available memories
        with their free memory / total memory.\n\n This is also present for apps and processes,
         so you know hows your system is running</string>
    <string name="tutorial_login">\n\nJust optional, but makes you files more secure from others</string>
    <string name="tutorial_navigation">Navigation pane lets you navigate from where ever you are to where ever you want.\n\n
        Swipe from left and you can see the navigation pane. It can come very handy</string>
    <string name="tutorial_features">Lot of unique features in AnExplorer\n
        1.Folder sizes\n
        2.Preview for media files including audio\n
        3.Language change from within the app\n
        4.Themes you can choose from\n</string>
    <string name="tutorial_apps">Manage all your apps that are installed.\n Make backup of your apps.
        You can also delete the app if you dont like them</string>
    <string name="tutorial_process">Manage all your apps that are running. \n
        You can stop the apps to clear up the memory</string>
    <string name="tutorial_hidden">One unique feature of AnExplorer.\n
        Hide any folder from showing up in the gallery. You can easily unhide them whenever you want</string>
    <string name="tutorial_wallpaper">Set wallpaper from all the wallpapers, picture etc.\n
        You can also set changing background automatically with bunch of wallpapers.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_explore">\n Jai Hind \\m/ Peace \\m/ \n\n
        Lot of stuff? Very less? Impressive? Unimpressive?\n
        Like our app? love it? hate it? have suggestion?\n\n
        We would love to hear from you.</string>

</resources>